{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The building construction industry relies on sets of ________ drawings to construct homes and commercial buildings.", "opta": "mechanical", "optb": "isometric", "optc": "architectural working", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The text height for room names should be set to ________for a drawing that will be plotted to a scale of \u00bc\" = 1'-0\".", "opta": "4\"", "optb": "5\"", "optc": "6\"", "optd": "8\"", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The architectural drafter usually begins a set of working drawings by creating the ________ plan first.", "opta": "foundation", "optb": "floor plan", "optc": "elevations", "optd": "building section", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Once the architect has finalized the house plans with the client any changes to the design requested by the client will require a ________.", "opta": "change order", "optb": "modification slip", "optc": "whole new set of drawings", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The foundation contractor will work with the following architectural plans.", "opta": "foundation", "optb": "site plan", "optc": "floor plan", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To insure that everyone understands what the electrical symbols represent it is customary to include a ____ on the electrical sheet.", "opta": "list", "optb": "part number", "optc": "electrical legend", "optd": "electrical layer", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "On a floor plan the dashed line that appears approximately 24\" outside the exterior wall represents the ________.", "opta": "sidewalk", "optb": "roof overhang", "optc": "plumbing drain lines", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The site plan illustrates ________.", "opta": "the floor plan", "optb": "where the house sits on the property", "optc": "the roof plan", "optd": "where the garage and driveway are located", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Generally, the units used on an architectural drawing are set to ________.", "opta": "Architectural", "optb": "engineering", "optc": "metric", "optd": "civil", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Elevation drawings will include information about ________.", "opta": "roof pitch", "optb": "siding", "optc": "window style", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}